noregisterads.co.tv 2018-01-07

# Co.TV domain names. Free Set Up: URL forwarding, DNS set up, Zone records or Free Sitebuilder.

**Privacy Policy**

This text is the privacy policy of the site named [www.co.tv](http://www.co.tv/). If you feel that the site performs an application contrary to this privacy policy, please contact us. 

REG2C.COM INC. 

_E-mail:_ info@co.tv 

**Information Collecting and Using**

REG2C.COM INC. collects information from users in various sections of the site and it is the only owner of all information collected in [www.co.tv](http://www.co.tv/) site. Information collected in the site cannot be sold, leased or given to third parties other than the ways explained in this text. However such information are sent to related bodies in case of request from legal/public authorities. 

**Register**

User must fill a register form first in order to become a member of this site. During registration, the user is requested to give information about his company/himself contact details (phone, e-mail etc.) and company profile and products. Such information may be used to inform users about our new products and services, and determining the member profile. 

**User Name and Password**

The account of the user can only be reached via the user name and password belonging to itself. 

**Publishing Commercial Information**

Commercial request information the user leaves in the site are open for use of all site users. This case must be considered while leaving personal information in this area. 

**Updating the Information**

The user may delete or change information about himself in the site anytime via the links in the Members Area. An e-mail must be sent to info@co.tv for the cancellation of membership. 

**Sharing the Information**

Demographic information relating to users may be shared with the advertisers of the site; such sharing does not contain transfer of personal information of users. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are used in our site in order to prevent our users from entering their user information again and again, and in order to make the site more comfortably useable. Cookies do not lead to identification of users. Functions of cookies end as soon as the window is closed. 

**Log Files**

IP adresses are used for the purpose of site management, seeing the trends, watching user movements, demographic information collection to increase usage. IP addresses do not enable us to identify the user. In case IP addresses are requested to be given to public/legal authorities, they are provided to those authorities. 

**Links**

There are link to other sites from this site. REG2C.COM INC. is not responsible for contents and privacy policies of other sites, links of which are given in this site. 

**Competitions and Questionnaires**

We want information from users for questionnaires, competitions and sweepstakes from time to time. Attending such questionnaires and competitions are optional, and it is up to the user’s decree to give information. The requested information may contain contact information (name, address, email, etc) and demographic information (age, gender, etc.). Contact information is used to notify the winner about his winnings and to give award. Questions of questionnaires are used to watch the use of the site and evaluate the pleasure gained from the site. 

**Order**

We want information from the user in our Order Forms. The user must give contact information (name, address, email, etc) and financial information (credit card no, expiration date etc.) in these sections. This information will be used to receive the payment of the user’s order, to deliver the order and to issue an invoice. If problems arise in payment or delivery, such information will be used to contact with the user. 

**Security**

Any kind of measurements are taken fort he security of information belonging to the user. When the user is giving credit card information via the web site, such information is encoded by SSL technology. Browser is locked when the user is in reliable page such as order form. 

**Amendments of Privacy Policy;**

[www.co.tv](http://www.co.tv/) reserves its rights to amend or cancel the Privacy Policy. It announces any new policy here. The user must visit this section frequently if he wants to be notified of the amendments.
